# MUHAMMAD ALI FERDIANSYAH

LABORATORY ASSISTANT



Jalan Benteng Somba Opu Kab.Gowa, Makassar 92161 Indonesia



+6285757103185



Zailyanzali@gmail.com

#### EDUCATION

OF SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL
SMAN 9 GOWA,
MAKASSAR
2018

STUDENT

UNIVERSITAS DIPA MAKASSAR

## SUMMARY

I am a highly motivated individual with a strong enthusiasm for learning and working on various projects. With experience as a freelance web developer, I possess solid technical skills and the ability to work independently as well as part of a team. I believe that effective collaboration and good communication are key to achieving the best results.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

● INSTRUCTOR | JUL 2022 - AGT 2022

SMPN 33 BULUKUMBA

INSTRUCTOR | DES 2022 - JAN 2023
SMPN 1 BANGKALA BARAT

CHIEF LABORATORY ASSISTANT | SEP 2022 - NOW UNIVERSITAS DIPA MAKASSAR

#### SKILLS

Microsoft Office

Algorthms

Front-end Web

Back-end Web

PHP

Javascript

Laravel

Tailwind CSS

#### **FXTRACURRICULAR**

**● EDUCATION DEPARTMENT | MEI 2023 - NOW** 

DIPANEGARA COMPUTER CLUB

#### LINK

Website:

zaily.netlify.app

Linkedin:

ferdiansyah7179

#### CERTIFICATE

LABORATORY ASSISTANT | MAKASSAR | JUL 2024

UNIVERSITAS DIPA MAKASSAR

● ALIBABA HACKATHON | MAKASSAR | AGT 2024

ALIBABA CLOUD

**● INTRUCTOR | BULUKUMBA | JAN 2022** 

DIPANEGARA COMPUTER CLUB